Anubhav Mahna anubhavmahna@gmail.com +91-9873397417

My expertise, multilateral experience, international exposure, and professional dedication for a Progressive, dynamic and challenging role, may contribute significantly and cause an effective role on the road of success for self and the esteemed organization.

Personnel Details:

Name: Anubhav Mahna

Permanent Address in India: Sec-23rd / H 96, Raj Nagar

Ghaziabad (U.P), India

Email Id: anubhavmahna@gmail.com

Work Experience

# Senior Sales Manager

GALAXY ONLINE POWER SYSTEM PVT Ltd (UPS & SERVO STABILIZER SYSTEM Manufacture)
April 2023 Till Date

- Working with GALAXY ONLINE POWER SYSTEM Pvt Ltd. manufacture of UPS & SERVO STABILIZER system. Handling product categories including UPS & Stabilizer and responsible for drive revenue for them.
- Leading strong growth in underperforming 500 KVA & 300 KVA product category of UPS and Stabilizer.
- Made Strong presence and progress in strategic segments where we weak like Builders, Hotels, Banks, Educations, and more.
- Setup a channel network of 20+ Systems Integrators (SI) and Strategic tie up with PMC for Targeting Govt Segment. Established the "Galaxy" brand across Corporate, Govt and Institutes.
- Exceeded Annual Individual target of INR 5 Crores.
- Participated in regular business reviews and manage follow up with a clear action plan for achieving Sales Target.
- Maintained MIS records and prompt follow-up for timely collection of payments.
- Strong Interface between the End customers, Operation team and the Senior Leadership

# Sales Manager

FABCON INDIA PVT Ltd (SNACK PROCESSING AND PACKAGING SYSTEM Manufacture)
March 2022 to April 2023

#### Job Profile:

- Working with FABCON INDIA Pvt Ltd. manufacturing machines of Snack food processing and packaging line system. Specialization in complete automatic processing line for snacks packaging, product conveying and distribution system.
- Areas regularly working with the Top Snack Manufacture & OEM Companies in the Food & FMCG segment. Companies like. Haldiram's, PepsiCo, ITC, Kellogg's, Perfetti, Bikano and more.
- .Job Description: -
- (1) CRM Handling (Customer Relationship Management Software)
- (2) Direct Calling for lead Generation
- (3) Sales Team Coordination
- (4) Dealing with the existing customer
- (5) Meeting with customer for Product Demonstration
- (6) Business Revenue
- (7) Quotations Follow-ups, Payments and Orders
- (8) Daily report
- · Meet sales target identified by upper management
- Maximize revenue growth by meeting daily, monthly and quarterly revenue goals

## Sales Manager

RECO MACHINE CO. (Magnetic Particle Inspection I.e. Magnaflex) August 2019 to February 2022

- Working with Reco Machine Co. manufacture of Magnetic Particle inspection Machine i.e MAGNAFLEX as Senior Sales Manager, Reco Machine Co provides physical checks and functional testing of Raw material to the finished product as per the International standards of Auto Mobile companies in Delhi-Ncr.
- Product handled (Florescent powder oil & water based, Carrier oil, Ultra Violet LED light, ASTM checking for crack detector, Centrifuge tube for checking the strength of florescent powder, De-Magnetizer tunnel type, trolley type, Automatic features Auto Clamp-De clamp, Auto Spray, Auto Magnetize, Gauss meter Etc)
- .Job Description: -

- (1) Client Handling
- (2) Product Explanation and Marketing
- (3) Lead Generation
- (4) Handling the existing client
- (5) Product Demonstration
- (6) Business Revenue
- (7) Sales Team Coordination
- Meet sales target identified by upper management
- Participate in team meetings to discuss progress, plans, and other activities
- Maximize revenue growth by meeting daily, monthly and quarterly revenue goals

# **Manager Sales**

Auric Solutions Pvt Ltd April 2015 to July 2018

- Worked with Auric Solutions System Integration Company, as a Senior Sales Manager, Experienced IT Sales Professional with ten years' experience in IT Infrastructure and IT project outsourcing.
- As Senior Sales Manager for global leader in IT field billions of global information technology firm, an entrepreneurial environment. Identified opportunities through continuous Information Technology business development.
- Marketing and leadership positions, building record of success in developing marketing campaigns, strategies and solutions that generated 8 Figure Revenue Growth, well- versed in marketing and sales lifecycles, skilled negotiator and strategist. Able to build relationships with high- level Personnel close large sales in heavily competitive environments with (Antara Group, SRS Group, Shristi Group, Hospitality Industries, Marriott, Taj, Starwood, MNC companies etc.)
- Experience of selling communications, IT hardware, voice applications, broadband connections, microchips, network applications, services, data, software and cloud based technologies
- Meet sales target identified by upper management Provide detailed information about technical specifications of products marketed by the company
- Attend industry events that are aimed at improving the marketability of the company's products and services
- Participate in team meetings to discuss progress, plans, and other activities

## Sales Manager

AL WATAN GROUP - Abu Dhabi, AE October 2013 to March 2015

#### Job Profile:

AlWatan Group, Abu Dhabi offers IT clients a complete package including commissioning of subcontracts, supply of components, cabling, installation & commissioning. Our skilled staffs have experience gained from the successful completion of Major installations in Oil & Gas Sector. Our Cabling Engineers are specialized in Structured Cabling Systems. We terminate and certify Cat5, Cat6, Cat7 and Fibber Optic cables from each outlet back to a cabinet or patch panel ensuring that all cabling is installed neatly and reliably.

## Responsibilities

- Prospect for potential new clients and turn this into increased business
- Plan approaches and pitches
- Build relationships with new clients
- Present new products and services and enhance existing relationships
- Forecast sales targets and ensure they are met by the sales team
- Track and record activity on accounts and help to close deals to meet these targets Identify opportunities for campaigns, products and distribution channels that will lead to an increase in sales

# Sales Manager

FCS Computer System Pte Ltd July 2010 to August 2013

- Worked with FCS Computer Systems Pte. Ltd, as a Sales Manager, high impact presentation, team building leadership, client, fulfilment, integrated sales and marketing plans, product line development.
- Marketing and leadership positions, building record of success in developing marketing campaigns, strategies and solutions that generated 7-8 Figure Revenue Growth, well- versed in marketing and sales lifecycles, skilled negotiator and strategist. Able to build relationships with high- level Personnel close large sales in heavily competitive environments. Experience in managing all core functions within a business.
- Product handled in Win Suite, Win Voice, PMS, POS, E-Connect etc in major group of hotels (Taj,Oberoi's, Starwood, Hilton, Radisson, Shangri-La-India)
- Direct reporting to the Country Head of the organization.
- International business exposure Attended seminar and training held in Thailand.

# **Asst. Sales Manager**

Shangri-La Hotel - Delhi, Delhi June 2005 to June 2010

#### Job Profile:

Highly talented and resourceful Hotel Room Sales Manager with great experience in developing and implementing total sales and marketing effort for hotels, including securing new accounts, maintaining existing accounts, and assist in executing sales and marketing strategies to maximize the profitability of the hotel while maintaining customer satisfaction • Hospitality industry experience: sales, planning, customer service, management and operations, development, and training • Excellent interpersonal communication skills with executives, colleagues, and clients • Proven ability to maintain relationships with new and existing clients • Detail oriented with proven ability to follow tasks through completion

- Ability to understand core objectives and challenges of company and department
   Ability to plan, prioritize and execute projects in a timely manner
- Proven ability to maintain sales and revenue by generating repeat and new business
- Maximize revenue growth by meeting daily, monthly and quarterly revenue goals

Education

Bachelor in Computer Application (BCA)
IGNOU - Delhi, Delhi
CBSE in Commerce Stream
Ghaziabad Public School - Ghaziabad, Uttar Pradesh

Skills

EXCEL, MICROSOFT WINDOWS, POWERPOINT, WINDOWS 98, WORD etc,

Additional Information

# Computer Skills:

- Operating System: Window 95 / Windows 98
- Packages: MS-Office (Excel, Word, PowerPoint)

Anubhay Mahna